Teacher: Hello?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Sorry?
You’re on mute.
Micaela: Is it OK now?
Teacher: Yes, fine now!
Hello, I’m Harry, from English House Language School.
Micaela: Hi, Harry.
Teacher: Hi, there.
OK, can I check your details first?
Micaela: Yes, of course.
Teacher: What’s your first name?
Micaela: Micaela.
Teacher: How do you spell it?
Micaela: M-I-C-A-E-L-A.
Teacher: M-I-C-A-E-L-A – is that right?
Micaela: Yes, that’s right.
Teacher: And … what’s your last name?
Micaela: Vazquez.
Teacher: Vazquez. Is that V-A-S…?
Micaela: No, it’s V-A-Z-Q-U-E-Z
Teacher: V-A-Z-Q-U-E-Z.
OK. Uh, how old are you, Micaela?
Micaela: I’m 25.
Teacher: Where are you from?
Micaela: I’m from Argentina.
Teacher: Where in Argentina?
Micaela: From Buenos Aires.
Teacher: What’s your address?
Micaela: It’s Florida one six five.
Teacher: Florida’s the street name?
Number one six five?
Micaela: Yes.
Teacher: What’s your zip code?
Micaela: Sorry?
Teacher: You know, the zip code.
Micaela: Ah yes.
It’s C-1-0-0-5-A-A-C.
Teacher: C-1-0-0-5-A-A-C.
Great.
What’s your email address?
Micaela: It’s m.vazquez@mail.com.
Teacher: And what’s your phone number?
Micaela: My cell phone or my home phone, my landline?
Teacher: Both – cell and landline.
Micaela: My cell is +54 – that’s for Argentina –
then 11 15 8934 5568.
Teacher: +54 11 15 8934 5568.
Great.
And your landline?
Micaela: +54 11 6023 5442.
Teacher: +54 11 6023 5442.
Micaela: That’s right.
Teacher: OK, that’s great.
So, what do you do, Micaela?
Micaela: I’m in college.
I’m a medical student.